<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Article on Hugo tranquilpeak theme</title>
    <link>https://weili-git.github.io/categories/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Article on Hugo tranquilpeak theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 22:58:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://weili-git.github.io/categories/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Annoying Scissors</title>
      <link>https://weili-git.github.io/2021/12/annoying-scissors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 22:58:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weili-git.github.io/2021/12/annoying-scissors/</guid>
      <description>When I was in college, I bought a pair of scissors in the supermarket. It&amp;rsquo;s durable and handy. Every time I use it to cut things, an inexplicable &amp;ldquo;sense of fulfillment&amp;rdquo; flooded into my heart. Although it is merely an ordinary pair of scissors, with the increase of use, I seem to have &amp;ldquo;relied&amp;rdquo; on it. Why do you say that? Because there are many times that I spend a lot of time finding it, even though several other scissors are at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Do List</title>
      <link>https://weili-git.github.io/2021/11/to-do-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 19:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weili-git.github.io/2021/11/to-do-list/</guid>
      <description>Homepage add publish time simplfy the layout page support search Navigator navigation link Categories list categories add sidebar cat navigate Live2d baisc function switch model Markdown Mathjax In progress.. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Details</title>
      <link>https://weili-git.github.io/2021/10/details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 12:57:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weili-git.github.io/2021/10/details/</guid>
      <description>Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough.
Link to another page.
Link to blog1.
Read Me.
There should be whitespace between paragraphs.
There should be whitespace between paragraphs. We recommend including a README, or a file with information about your project.
Header 1 This is a normal paragraph following a header. GitHub is a code hosting platform for version control and collaboration. It lets you and others work together on projects from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
